{
    "subject": "resource/Spider-Man_Unlimited",
    "predicate": "property/episodenumber",
    "object": "10",
    "human_readable": "The episode number of Spider-Man Unlimited is 10.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7264313697814941,
            "question": "How many episodes are there in Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7242746353149414,
            "question": "What is the episode number of the final episode of Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5102482438087463,
            "question": "Do you know any details about the plot of Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45710861682891846,
            "question": "Where can I watch episodes of Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3780418932437897,
            "question": "Is there a sequel to Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37134850025177,
            "question": "Is Spider-Man Unlimited a long or short series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35088542103767395,
            "question": "Who are some of the characters featured in Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2905244529247284,
            "question": "What year was Spider-Man Unlimited released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2729402482509613,
            "question": "Are there any popular themes explored in Spider-Man Unlimited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26799896359443665,
            "question": "What makes Spider-Man Unlimited unique compared to other Spider-Man shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The episode number of Spider-Man Unlimited is 10.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3287_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular themes explored in Spider-Man Unlimited?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3287_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Spider-Man Unlimited released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3287_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the characters featured in Spider-Man Unlimited?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3287_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3287_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the number of episodes of Spider-Man Unlimited, stating that it had 13 episodes. Therefore, the statement claiming the episode number is 10 is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}